import '../models/question_model.dart';

final List<QuestionsModel> questions = [
  QuestionsModel(
    question: "What is the capital city of Saudi Arabia?",
    a: "Jeddah",
    b: "Riyadh",
    c: "Dammam",
    d: "Mecca",
    answer: "B",
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question: "In which year was Saudi Arabia founded?",
    a: "1902",
    b: "1912",
    c: "1932",
    d: "1952",
    answer: "C",
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question: "Which desert covers most of Saudi Arabia?",
    a: "Gobi Desert",
    b: "Sahara Desert",
    c: "Thar Desert",
    d: "Rub' al Khali (Empty Quarter)",
    answer: "D",
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question: "What is the official language of Saudi Arabia?",
    a: "Arabic",
    b: "Urdu",
    c: "English",
    d: "Turkish",
    answer: "A",
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question: "What is the currency of Saudi Arabia?",
    a: "Riyal",
    b: "Dinar",
    c: "Dirham",
    d: "Pound",
    answer: "A",
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question: "What is the main religion practiced in Saudi Arabia?",
    a: "Christianity",
    b: "Hinduism",
    c: "Islam",
    d: "Buddhism",
    answer: "C",
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question: "Which holy city in Saudi Arabia do millions of Muslims visit annually?",
    a: "Medina",
    b: "Jeddah",
    c: "Mecca",
    d: "Taif",
    answer: "C",
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question: "Saudi Arabia is known for being the world's largest exporter of what resource?",
    a: "Natural gas",
    b: "Coal",
    c: "Petroleum (Oil)",
    d: "Gold",
    answer: "C",
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question: "Which Saudi Arabian city is known as the 'Gateway to the Two Holy Mosques'?",
    a: "Jeddah",
    b: "Riyadh",
    c: "Medina",
    d: "Mecca",
    answer: "A",
  ),
  QuestionsModel(
    question: "Which body of water lies to the west of Saudi Arabia?",
    a: "Arabian Sea",
    b: "Red Sea",
    c: "Persian Gulf",
    d: "Mediterranean Sea",
    answer: "B",
  ),
];
